Jinguji!
Are you trying to get crushed to death?
I'm sorry, Tachibana.
I had no idea I'd been
causing you all this pain.
Whoa, you okay?
The thing is, in my entire life
I've never once praised anyone.
Even now I can't do it.
I don't know how.
Then you might suck as a person?
Chartsie, stay out of this!
What?
Now that's cheating All of my
direct attacks just get deflected.
I'll knock off the arms if I punch again!
Right?
How do you like this?
Those thoughts, I think maybe
it's true that I suck as a person.
Go ahead, you're still stuck on
that when we're about to die?
How can I help when I end up hurting
people just by being around them?
I never considered that
what I thought was helpful
criticism could come off as
judgmental or patronizing,
but if someone mistook my intent,
of course they would be hurt by it.
Jigun!
Jigunji, help me!
And for it to come from someone you
consider to be your best friend,
someone you believe is
better than you in every way?
it's no wonder Tachibana
is in so much pain.
I think it would be best if
I disappeared from his life.
Weren't you listening to
a single word he said?
Huh?
He literally just told you.
The only thing he takes pride in is
the fact that you're his best friend.
So even though he's completely
unhinged and trying to kill us,
you're still important to him.
It's hard for people to admit
what they really care about,
especially when they're in a bad place.
Him opening up like this is a huge deal!
And if you were to walk out on him
now after everything that's happened,
you wouldn't be protecting him,
you'd be hurting him all over again!
Ethan, what am I supposed to do?
He's been telling you what
to do this whole time!
He wants you to compliment
him, so just do it already!
I thought I did, but it
just made him angrier.
That's because what you told
him didn't mean anything to you!
He needs to know how you
feel from the bottom of your
heart something that shows
him how important he is to you
Do you think I don't get that?
But still...
Come on!
This shouldn't be that hard for you!
Well...
Isn't it embarrassing to
confess something like that?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
Hey, what was that for?!
SHUT UP!
Your bizarre lover's quarrel
is endangering a whole kingdom!
Imagine how it feels for all of us!
Lover's claw?
You're a thirty-something-year-old man,
but you've been acting like a whiny teen!
You even got jealous because the princess
started hanging out with Tachibana!
I already told you, I
wasn't jealous! That's it!
That's the problem right there!
You can't admit you're
jealous or care about him
when it's a totally normal
guy-friend thing to do!
It's normal?
So that means you felt that way?
With a man?
Seriously?
When my friend Yamazato stopped hanging
out with me after he got a girlfriend,
I got stupid jealous, but I dealt
with it like a normal person!
Keeping Tachipane at arm's
length because he's a
dude is weirder than
admitting he's special to you!
And you being self-conscious about the
whole thing only adds to the weirdness.
I see. Thank you.
I think I finally understand.
As a child, I was taught
to never rely on others.
Those who did were seen
as selfish or spoiled.
Never falter.
Carry yourself with dignity.
Be the example to society.
These ideas were drilled into me.
Never appear as weak.
Never show vulnerability.
That was how I could become strong
enough to survive the world on my own.
I came to believe that if I were to bare
my soul, I'd be risking myself for nothing.
But...
Guys can be jealous over each other!
It's a completely normal thing!
You agree? What? Oh, yeah! Of course!
You can do what you want!
I think I will!
Got him!
It's high time I let myself be honest.
I owe that much to my best friend.
That and more, right, Schwartz? Ha!
One thousand percent!
Why are you doing this?
I've kept this paint
bottled up for so long!
The least you can do is
let me take it out on you!
Why try this hard to stop me?!
And all I really want to do is
feel a little better about myself!
I've always envied you, Tachibana.
You make friends everywhere you go,
and no matter where you might be,
you're always surrounded by smiles.
Just being part of your life
is enough to warm my heart.
Earlier you said you were sick of
being a person who has nothing.
How could you think that when your life
is filled with so much more than mine?
I wish you could see what I see in you.
And yet, after all your years together,
you still don't have a clue
about how he truly feels.
Why would you trust anything he says?
He's never been truly honest with you.
You know how clever he is.
Imagine how easy it would be for
him to hide his true feelings.
Just like how you were able to hide
your jealousy of him all this time.
That's right.
I bet deep down you're just laughing
at how much of a loser I am.
The loser who's jealous
of his best friend,
who complains about how
unfair the world is?
because he doesn't have
any special talents.
It didn't matter what I did.
I never lasted long.
The most I ever do is moan about
all the things I failed at.
Meanwhile, you're out there
being perfect at everything.
The difference between us was clear.
You've earned tons of
awards and certificates.
You're a student council
president and the student rep.
And you're stupid popular.
You never tolerated bullies or thugs.
You saved those who
couldn't save themselves.
I realized all of this the moment
we met back in grade school.
You never talked at all, but
you still stood up for me.
I didn't even know your name.
Hey there, are you okay?
Oh yeah, I was jealous.
All this time, I wanted
to be just like you.
Because to me.
So cool.
Leo, you look just like a hero!
You are a hero!
And I look up to you!
Do you think it's weird?
Sorta.
I mean, wanting to be that
when you grow up is kinda...
But hey, if it's what you
wanna do, that's cool.
A hero.
Oh, it sounds like Mepon is shutting down.
Oh, does that touch Ivana?
Yeah, that's him.
Hang on a second.
What is it doing now?
Is this bad?
Sounds like an error warning.
Error! Error!
Unknown interference with
energy source detected!
Initiate.
Transformation.
To Resos Mode.
Commencing extermination of all life
forms in the immediate vicinity.
What's going on?
Nothing good.
Things just got worse!
I think these are homing targets,
they'll stay on us no matter what!
Seems like it.
What are we gonna do now?
Riso's smoke sounds scary enough, but now
we got literal targets on our foreheads.
It's game over, man! Calm down.
This doesn't change anything.
Our goals are still the same.
First, we're going to rescue Tachibana.
After which, I'll destroy
Mepon before anyone is hurt.
But I can't do it alone.
So...
Are you ready?
Schwarz!
I've got your back!
Nice try! Take this!
Now, Chinko-Chi! Right!
Of all the things that crappy goddess
has done, she outdid herself with this!
Give me back!
My best friend!
You alright, Tachibana?
You look like you just got off a bender.
Hey, are you okay?
Jiguchi?
Darn it!
I let my guard down!
I forgot how dangerous
those teary eyes can be!
I'm sorry, you must think I'm pathetic
acting like a bratty child at my age.
I really screwed up.
You could have gotten killed, and I
nearly destroyed the entire kingdom!
I let myself get caught
up in a dumb rebellion
and ended up going on a robot rampage.
I'm a garbage person.
You have every reason to hate me.
And I understand if you don't
want me in your life anymore.
Tachibana, I'm only
going to say this once.
So please listen.
I think that you're amazing
and you're a good person.
You're very considerate.
You never forget to follow up with people.
You always pay attention
and learn their needs.
No matter what people might ask of
you, you give it to them in the end.
You make friends easily, which to
me is a sign of good character.
And it's something that
I've never been able to do.
You're kind, and though bosses tend to
hate you, your juniors all love you.
You have an upbeat attitude.
Your smile brightens my day,
and you're an expressive person.
Animals love to be around you.
You never get full of yourself.
You replace the toilet paper in
the bathroom when the rolls out.
You're smarter than you give yourself
credit for, and you are athletic!
You just think you're not because
you compare yourself to me.
I've had dark times I couldn't
have gotten through without you.
I admire your empathy and your bizarre
ability to get people to laugh at anything,
like your terrible jokes.
When you're around, the world is brighter,
and that saved me from many a bad day.
You have the best ugly cry,
especially when you watch videos of
cute animals or kids doing errands.
And when something is clearly staged,
you can love it unapologetically.
I like how you'll try
popular things just because.
And after you found out I liked whiskey,
you always kept some on hand
despite hating it yourself.
I like how easy it is for
you to praise someone,
even if you don't think you deserve any.
And when you see someone meet with
misfortune, you always feel bad for them.
I like that you cry for your friends,
but still go out of your way to understand
and respect people's boundaries.
You are by far the most loyal and
empathetic person I have ever met.
You're oblivious to when others
hate you, so you don't reciprocate,
though that obliviousness
can get you in trouble.
I like that whenever you go out to eat,
you go out of your way to
tell the staff that they
did a good job and how
much you enjoyed the food.
I like how much fun you can have when you're
at cultural festivals or doing sports,
and how unexpectedly upset
you can get when you lose.
I like that you think the unluckiest
fortune is actually lucky.
Animals don't just like
you, they're drawn to you.
I like that you always share
videos you think are funny,
and how you can't stand horror movies
but force yourself through them anyway.
I like that somehow you never
have a handkerchief on you,
but you always make sure to have bandages.
Your terrible taste in women and that
you're weirdly childlike I like that!
You'll say it's a good day
just because the morning
weather is nice and the way
you like Hokkaido and Okinawa?
I like that despite how much
you complain about them.
You care for your family more
than anything I like how much
you love kids and your tendency
to spoil your younger sister.
I like that no matter how upset
you get you're over in a week that
you ask before squeezing lemon
over karage and that you can tell.
When I'm nervous and always know
exactly what to say to help me relax?
I like that you always have fun when I
take you shopping even if it's somewhere.
that's not your style.
I like that you unabashedly
say the most embarrassing
things and how being around
me seems so effortless.
I like how you say everything
you eat is delicious,
especially since you
don't like green peppers.
I like how you can't finish
your sentences when you're
drunk or how you'll give
up your seat on a train.
I like that you're so much better
at drawing than I am and how
diligent you are with properly
shaving your face each and every day.
I like that you always make sure
to say thank you for this meal
and the way you make up your mind
when you commit to something.
So all in all, I would have
to say to me, on any scale,
you rate much higher than
the Average person would
you like me to keep going
oh thank you what didn't
you tell me that you wanted
me to praise you more deal
with it once i get started
i can't stop myself okay
yeah all right that was too much why did
you have to go so far
for so long it was nice
for a while but you kept going and going
are you embarrassed of course i am you jerk
Hey, why did you start
laughing all of a sudden?
It's kind of creepy.
Huh? Oh, sorry.
I was just thinking, it's
nice to be honest with myself.
Right then, ready to go?
Yeah, I'm ready.
This guy...
I didn't know he could laugh like that.
Huh?
Something wrong?
No, no good.
Warning!
Damage to critical system detected.
Unit P-5-8, self-destruct
sequence initiated.
I'm out.
I'm stealing some of your karaka, Hina.
You can have some of mine.
I am so sorry.
Not just for kidnapping and
endangering your daughter,
but also for my part in helping her create
a full-blown rebellion
against the kingdom.
Honored hero.
It is I who should apologize
for the actions of my daughter.
No! It was me! It was all me!
I'll take any punishment!
No, please understand.
This all started with my daughter,
and she should be held responsible.
You don't have anything to apologize for.
Sorry, but half of this
was directly your fault.
It's hardly unusual for a human to
make a mistake or two in their life.
Scary how easily you can look back on this
whole nightmare and say, Oopsie daisy!
Oh, Iggy, you've grown up into
such an exceptional young lady!
If the king's happy, then
I guess everything's fine?
Actually, a simple answer to something
this complicated might be best.
If that maid hadn't been
promoted or hired at all,
if Tachibana hadn't followed the princess,
or if Muriya had managed
to rescue either of them?
mistakes were made all around.
So for clarity's sake, I say we
should blame it on the head maid.
Blame the head maid, you say?
Both she and Viz admitted they've
been working with the demon lord.
I wouldn't be surprised if
she was behind everything.
Well that wasn't according to plan.
I thought we'd be able to
take over this kingdom easily.
But I guess I was wrong about that.
I want to go home.
This sucked.
I just want the demon lord to find
my head and make it all better.
Then it seems you and I have same idea.
For once let's go home.
Let's go.
Never had I imagined that we would
be attacked so directly like this.
But as the goddess said this is no
time for the kingdom to go to war.
All the more reason for
us to defeat the demon
lord as quickly as possible
for everyone's benefit.
Yeah yeah.
Do you have to?
You've only just got here.
I guess we should.
Since the demon lord's
forces know we're here.
We'd only cause more trouble if we stayed.
It'd be best for everyone if
we left as soon as we can.
So we'll head out tomorrow.
I see.
I finally make a friend.
I have to let her go so
quickly after we met.
Iggy...
Don't worry about it.
Think of this as a chance
to make more friends.
You've got a great personality.
If you could be friends
with someone like me,
I'm sure you'll have no
problem thinking more.
Hero...
Tachibana, please don't talk
about yourself like that.
It's good to lift others up
but you shouldn't have to put
yourself down you deserve to
be treated with kindness and
respect just like anyone else
being considerate of others
doesn't mean you shouldn't expect
the same in return okay i get
it i take it all back we need
to hurry up and defeat the
demon lord so i can go back to
my old self the sooner we're on
the road the sooner that happens
isn't it weird that we've
come this far and we still have
no idea how to find the demon?
Lord? Huh?
Hey, Tachibana, did you say you don't
know how to find the Demon Lord?
I know where he is.
I could tell you how to get there.
You know? I do.
Wait, the goddess didn't tell you?
It was like
the first thing mine
showed me when I got here.
You see that big white
spire on the horizon, right?
Sad thing.
And you never told us?
Hey, I mean, it never came up, did it?
I just assumed you already Knew
she said the castle was near
the belly button so it's
probably around here at least we.
Have an idea where we
should be going that we
do it's been too long
since i've been home sweet.
Pillow of mine oh how
i've missed you tachibana
are you sure you're okay
with leaving tomorrow
it's for the best isn't it plus now we
know where we're supposed to go well after
everything that's happened i thought you'd
want to rest and there's
more stuff about the.
Religion i wanted to look into
plus we have the tiara back
so it wouldn't hurt to stay a
day or two yeah yeah i guess
we could stay a little longer
if that's good with you what
is wrong with me i can't even
look at him what's up nothing?
They're nothing!
I've...
everything's... good!
If there's something
wrong, you can tell me.
The two of us have already
been through so much.
Whatever you have to say, it'll be fun.
Come on, why are you
looking away like that?
Is there something on my face?
Did I say something strange?
No, it's got nothing to do with you.
I just started feeling kind of
weird all of a sudden, that's all.
You feel weird?
I see.
You do look a little red.
It might be a fever.
Do you feel sick at all?
It's possible that you're exhausted.
Let's take your temperature.
I'll get some blankets.
Are you thirsty?
Get off of me, man!
Your niceness is creeping me out!
And give me some space!
You've been all over me since we got back!
Then why did you change
in front of me next night?
Do it in the hallway!
Hey...
Tachibana...
above your head...
Heh.
Are you all right, Totswana?
Does it look like I'm all right to you?
Well, no, but how are you?
It's just because I'm tired!
That's the only possible reason!
Of course!
That makes perfect sense!
You're just tired, right?
So, this is where we say goodbye? Yep.
It's been quite the adventure.
Are you sure you don't
want to come with us?
It's your call to make, Schwartz.
We're in a whole other world.
I want to experience
as much of it as I can.
Though I'm sure we'll
see each other again.
We gotta get that Demon Lord.
In the end,
we warriors who have faced death
side by side will join forces again
in our final battle and crush our
great enemy with our combined might.
Sounds pretty awesome, don't you think?
Yeah, that's definitely how it'll go.
I'm grateful for the
time we've had together.
You two have taught me
more than I expected.
Now I know that I should never
let appearances deceive me.
And that it feels really good to hold
nothing back when you punch someone!
Seems like you're learning
the wrong lessons here?
Well, I must admit I'm a
little reluctant to part ways.
I kind of assumed you didn't
care one way or the other.
I do, I still owe him for that
punch he mentioned earlier!
I'm kidding.
You're not!
Yeah!
Who like the music?
Just helium to stop. Cute.
To play finally stop!
Love like that.
Love's no love?
Without a woman.
It's not what you need.
I'm not really.
You can't suck it.
I'm not hanging from looking at them.
I'm not hanging from the top.
Oh!
I'm out of late, you know.
Just go!
I'm out of late. We're not doing much.
I'm out of late.
No! I'm out of late.
Good, I'm out of late.
There is no love.
I'm out of late.
Right, shall we go? Uh-huh.
Come on, I know they can't!
I can't even look at them!
Dang it, this is bad.
Especially now that we know
both of us can be charmed.
What am I gonna do?
I'm barely keeping it together!
No one we're both susceptible
is making it hit harder!
I feel like I'm about to hurl!
What would happen if we both
became charmed at the same time?
And what would happen after
we came to our senses?
We can never let that happen!
We have to work together to make sure
we break this curse as soon as possible!
In that moment, their hearts
were once again joined as one.
Well, ready to go?
More than you even know.
Let's take that demon lord down.
Before I end up falling
in love with this guy.
And so continues this
romantic comedy between
a guy and someone who used to be a guy.